// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In the background picture of the entretainment topic that you just clicked, what does Russel Crow's caracter say in that scene of Gladiator?",
    answer: "Are you not entretained!",
    options: [
      "Are you having fun!",
      "Do I amuse you?",
      "Are you not entretained!",
      "Say hello to my little friend"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What eminent scientist hosted the television show Cosmos after Carl Sagan?",
    answer: "Neil Degrasse Tyson",
    options: [
      "Neil Degrasse Tyson",
      "Elon Musk",
      "Albert Einstein",
      "Stephen Hawking"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who is the author of Lord of the rings",
    answer: "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    options: [
      "C. S. Lewis",
      "J. R. R. Tolkien",
      "George R. R. Martin",
      "J. K. Rowling"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In which of these countries did manga originate?",
    answer: "Japan",
    options: [
      "Korea",
      "China",
      "Japan",
      "Russia"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Gangnam Style, a humourous pop song by South Korean singer Psy was released in which year?",
    answer: "2012",
    options: [
      "2010",
      "2012",
      "2014",
      "2020"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who is the lead singer of the band Coldplay",
    answer: "Chris Martin",
    options: [
      "Ryan Tedder",
      "Dan Reynolds",
      "Will Champion",
      "Chris Martin"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many oscars did Lord of the rings Return of the king (3rd movie) win?",
    answer: "11",
    options: [
      "5",
      "7",
      "9",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which character does Bryan Cranston play in the series Breaking Bad?",
    answer: "Walter White",
    options: [
      "Tony Soprano",
      "Michael Scofield",
      "Walter White",
      "Werner Heisenberg"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who played the leading actor in charlie and the chocolate factory ?",
    answer: "Johnny Depp",
    options: [
      "Johnny Depp",
      "Tom Cruise",
      "Brad Pitt",
      "Tom Holland"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who is the director behind Inception and Interstellar ",
    answer: "Christopher Nolan",
    options: [
      "Steven Spielberg",
      "Christopher Nolan",
      "David Finsher",
      "Denis Villeneuve"
    ]
  },
];